fashionesta.com 2017-09-23

# Privacy Policy / designer online shop

We appreciate your interest in our website. Protecting your privacy is very important to us. Below we provide detailed information on how we handle your data.

Collection, processing and use of personal data  
You can visit our site without disclosing any personal information. We only store data without reference to individuals. This data is used solely to improve our offer and permit no conclusion on your person. Personal data are only collected when you submit them in the context of your order or when opening a customer account or registering for our newsletter. We use this information without your explicit permission, solely for the processing of your order. With completion of the contract and full payment your data will be blocked for further use and deleted after the tax and commercial storage periods, unless you have explicitly consented to the further use of your data. When registering for our newsletter your e-mail address will be used for promotional purposes, until you unsubscribe from the newsletter. You can unsubscribe at any time.

Use of cookies  
On several pages, we use cookies to make visiting our website attractive and allow the use of certain functions. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer. Most of the cookies we use are deleted from your hard drive after your browser session ended (so called session-cookies). Our partner companies are not allowed to collect, process or use personal data via cookies on our website. 

Disclosure of personal data  
A transfer or your data is made to shipping companies to the extent which is necessary to deliver the goods. For the settlement of payment your payment details will be processed to the bank or agency respnsonsible for the payment.

Right of access to personal data  
According to the Federal Data Protection Act you have the right to get free information on your stored data and the right to rectify, block or delete your data.

Contact für Privacy Policy  

Privacy Statement  
For questions regarding the collection, processing or use of personal information, the disclosure, correction, blocking or deletion of data and revocation of consents granted, please contact:
